We will see the importance of the eye in the expression of the cranio-sacral system
我们将看到眼睛在颅骶系统表达中的重要性
and in neuronal memorization and also in tissue memorization.
以及在神经元记忆和组织记忆中的重要性。
This means that you can store memories anywhere in your body
这意味着你可以在身体的任何地方储存记忆
that are written by the eye.
这些记忆是由眼睛记录的。
If you don't know, for example, how to integrate them, you will somatize them.
如果你不知道如何整合它们，例如，你就会将它们躯体化。
What is not integrated is somatized.
未被整合的就会被躯体化。
Every time there is an eye, there is an eye, there is an eye.
每次有眼睛，就有眼睛，就有眼睛。
that I don't know how to solve a problem
我不知道如何解决一个问题
my body will memorize it
我的身体会记住它
but in its symbolism
但在其象征意义上
in its symbolism
在其象征意义上
where it will memorize it according to the spaces
它会根据空间来记忆它
that is, of space
也就是说，根据空间
mineral, plant, animal
矿物、植物、动物
or human
或人类
depending on the timing
根据时间
and the processes of coordination and synchronicity
以及协调和同步过程
so you're going to synchronize it
所以你会同步它
in your symbolism
在你的象征意义中
you're going to symbolize it
你会象征它
I'm three years old
我三岁了
and then you're going to put it in your symbolism
然后你会把它放入你的象征意义中
And I'm really scared.
我非常害怕。
My parents are leaving.
我父母出去了。
They leave me alone at home.
他们把我一个人留在家里。
I panicked.
我吓坏了。
I'm going to hide under the table.
我躲到桌子下面。
And then all of a sudden, I catch what we call colds.
然后突然间，我得了所谓的感冒。
I have maxillary sinuses.
我有上颌窦炎。
And in fact, we see that there is a synchronicity.
事实上，我们看到在
in the pneumatization spaces between the
肾上腺和我的上颌窦之间的气化空间中存在同步性。
adrenals and my maxillary sinuses.
肾上腺和我的上颌窦。
And later, this person comes with chronic sinusitis.
后来，这个人患有慢性鼻窦炎。
She symbolized an unresolved problem.
她象征了一个未解决的问题。
This is not where it is treated.
这不是在这里治疗的。
It is treated by releasing your adrenals.
它需要治疗，释放你的肾上腺。
Because what did the adrenals do?
因为肾上腺做了什么？
They have two...
它们有两个...
cortisol movement
皮质醇运动
in relation to stress.
与压力有关。
You're going to increase it.
你会增加它。
But there, you don't know how to do it well.
但现在，你不知道如何做好。
So, your adrenals are blocked.
所以，你的肾上腺被阻塞了。
Fears, in fact,
恐惧，实际上，
it's not so much the kidney.
并不是肾脏本身。
It's the cap on the kidneys.
而是肾脏上的“帽子”（指肾上腺）。
Same thing with, for example,
同样地，例如，
the thyroid and the frontal sinus.
甲状腺和额窦。
Around 7 years old,
大约在7岁时，
I know how to do it
我知道如何
front, by my voice, because the activity
通过我的声音来面对，因为
electrical activity of the lateroid is fully functional,
侧甲状腺的电活动已完全发挥作用，
that is to say, my vocal cords, my words have strength. And
也就是说，我的声带，我的话语都具有力量。然后
then there is still
还有
another one, it's the brain that descends into the testicles, around 12
另一个，就是大脑下降到睾丸，大约在12岁左右，
years old, where
那时，
we have what we call the pituitary phenomenon, in relation to
我们有所谓的垂体现象，与
pituitary pneumatization,
垂体气化有关，
the puberty axis, so these are
青春期的轴线，所以这些是
hormones, it happens
荷尔蒙，它同时发生，
at the same time, it will mature
会使性腺成熟
the gonads
并允许精子转化。
and allow the transformation of spermatozoa
这些是同步性的空间。
These are spaces of synchronicity.
在其他空间中，你有
In other spaces, you have spaces
象征化的空间。有时，
symbolization. Sometimes,
有些人被时间困住了。
these are people who are stuck in time.
实际上，有时你可能会被困住，当你
In fact, sometimes you can be stuck when you have
你有一个点，一个锚点，
You have a point, an anchor,
每当有现象发生时，
and every time there is a phenomenon
你就会重新激活视觉记忆
you reactivate the visual memory
或听觉记忆，但它非常视觉化，
or auditory, but it's very visual
人们有图像，
people have images
你明白吗？
you see
然后我们利用这些图像，
and then we use these images
通过一种非常棒的技术，
in a technique that is very nice
我们称之为快速眼动，
it's what we call rapid eye movement
我们在晚上进行，
that we do at night
为了尝试解决
to try to resolve
并建立系统。
and we use this in a technique called EMDR
我们将其用于一种称为 MDR 的技术中
so it doesn't remove the trauma
所以它不会消除你的创伤
but it gives you back this dissociation
但它会让你重新获得这种分离
this non-identification
这种非认同
but in fact these are memories
但实际上这些是记忆
and we do it with what? with the eyes
我们用什么来做呢？用眼睛
why will the eye make these movements?
为什么眼睛会做这些运动？
because it will go from your left brain
因为它会从你的左脑
to your right brain
到你的右脑
it will put back in the right box
它会把它们放回正确的位置
what is between the rational and the irrational
介于理性和非理性之间
between what is rational
介于理性
and intuitive
和直觉之间
you see?
你明白吗？
an imbalance
一种不平衡
someone who...
一个人如果...
too rational
过于理性
will have an imbalance
就会出现不平衡
pituitary.
垂体不平衡。
Someone who is
一个人如果
too intuitive all the time
总是过于直觉
will have a pituitary imbalance.
也会出现垂体不平衡。
It's like riding a bicycle.
这就像骑自行车。
The pituitary gland,
垂体，
it tries to do all that
它试图做所有这些
vis-à-vis the corpus callosum system
关于胼胝体系统
to pass on the information.
以传递信息。
In fact, it's a lot of information
实际上，这是一个重要的信息
that passes with the visual areas
通过视觉区域传递
in relation to eye movement.
与眼球运动相关。
that rebalance.
它们重新平衡。
They go tac, tac, tac, tac, tac, tac,
它们做哒、哒、哒、哒、哒、哒，
and we do that every night.
我们每晚都这样做。
I take, tac, all my baggage,
我拿起，哒，我所有的行李，
I rationalize, I put back,
我理性化，我放回去，
or I'm intuitive, I put back in the boxes.
或者我直觉，我放回盒子里。
Dreaming is very important.
梦想非常重要。
And we can use these eye movements,
我们可以利用这些眼球运动，
like heart coherence,
就像心脏一致性一样，
and things like that, all of that is important.
以及诸如此类的事情，所有这些都很重要。